http://www.educationlawadvocates.com/resources/privacy-policy.html

Privacy Policy: EducationLawAdvocates.com
EducationLawAdvocates.com understands that you want to browse the internet without giving up your personal information.
EducationLawAdvocates.com does not require or share your personal information with any other organizations.
Information About "Cookies"
The entities that advertise on EducationLawAdvocates.com may use ads that work with "cookies".
These tracking methods are used to track ad performance.
Cookies are simple tracking tools and are not designed display your personal information.
EducationLawAdvocates.com may use Google Adsense to display ads.
Google Adsense uses the DoubleClick Dart Cookie to analyze ad performance.
You can learn more about Adsense by visiting : the official Google Adsense site.
Also, you can prevent the use of cookies on your computer by visiting: the Network Advertising Opt Out Page.
Your IP Address
We have the right to track your IP address. We do this to allow for a more efficient search experience and protect our site from spamming attempts. Our IP database is provided by MaxMind.com.
You can contact us if you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy.
Tax Debt Help
Search Lawyers By Location
Additional Information
Tax Debt Protection Services
Hire a Tax Lawyer and Get Out of Tax Debt
How Tax Debt Impacts Your Credit
Optimizing Your Time When Working With a Lawyer
Reasons to Hire a Tax Debt Lawyer
Why is Credit Score Important?
Quick Links
Home
Lawyer Listings
Change Listing Requests
Add Your Business Listing
About Us
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
About Us
Contact Us
Disclaimer
This website is a web directory and referral service for lawyers. This website is not represented by an attorney. The information on this website is for general information only and shouldn't be used as official legal advice.
@Copyrights 2019 www.EducationLawAdvocates.com - All Rights Reserved.
